<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on tazik.sh</title>
    <link>https://zktkz.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on tazik.sh</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://zktkz.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>🔨 DIY</title>
      <link>https://zktkz.github.io/posts/diy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zktkz.github.io/posts/diy/</guid>
      <description>An assorted list of ordinary life improvements I&amp;rsquo;ve implemented.
⏰ DIY Light Alarm (Fig. 1) Pulley for blinds attached to the nightstand. This contraption is meant to make it easier to wake up in the morning. I initially tried using a mop as the supporting pole; but reemplacing it every time the floor needed to be sweeped was too much of a hassle, so I ended up abandoning it.
I was initially concerned that the stand would be unstable, but it worked out quite nicely.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HOW-TO: Switch Google Accounts Faster </title>
      <link>https://zktkz.github.io/posts/google/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zktkz.github.io/posts/google/</guid>
      <description>Switching Google accounts is a pain. If you&amp;rsquo;re logged in with account #1 and then want to switch to account #2, you have to drag your cursor to the bottom right corner of the screen, click on your profile icon to bring up the list of profiles, and then click on the desired account. The whole process can take 5-10 seconds, which is quite a bit of friction when you want to jot down a quick note.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>🎶 Spotify Free</title>
      <link>https://zktkz.github.io/posts/spotify/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zktkz.github.io/posts/spotify/</guid>
      <description>The free version of Spotify Mobile is rather limited &amp;ndash; one has restricted access to tracks, cannot move to an arbitrary point in a track, or play a track on repeat. I test how much I can optimize my Spotify experience without signing up for Premium (or selling out for an illegal crack).
Introduction Spotify Mobile only allows tracks to be played as part of a larger playlist of songs. I made a playlist with just one track, to see how Shuffle Play would deal with it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://zktkz.github.io/posts/thdne/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zktkz.github.io/posts/thdne/</guid>
      <description>Font, to some approximation
I perform transfer learning on the pre-trained Danbooru2019 Portraits Stylegan 2 model, to best girl.numbers don’t lie.Data Engineering Download desired images off of Danbooru using this tool (it might be worth saving by %id%, in case metadata is desired later on).
Hayasaka has ~270 images on Danbooru, and even with higher accuracy, it would still be a pretty small dataset. I am turning to Pixiv as an adjunct solution.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>